(Sheldon:)Still sounds like a lot
of unnecessary touching.
(Amy:)Trust me. With your right hand,
locate the spot
(Amy:)where the scapula meets
the acromion process.
(Sheldon:)All right.
(Amy:)Now push your third finger along
the ridge of the shoulder blade,
(Amy:)making a small rotation
as you do so.
(Sheldon:)Rotating.
(Amy:)You should feel
a small node-like object
(Amy:)rolling back and forth along
the bone.
(Sheldon:)You mean the myofascial point?
(Amy:)Obviously.
(Amy:)Now bear down on it like
the seventh grade noogies
(Amy:)we all know too well.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear Lord, yes, yes,
oh, yes!
(Sheldon:)Amy, I've never been touched
like this before!
Oh! My hands are magic!
(Amy:)Don't flatter yourself.
(Amy:)Your hands are blunt tools
guided by my knowledge
(Amy:)of the nervous system.
(Amy:)I could just as easily have
paralyzed you.